CIRO BOZZA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



+49 1578 5098335



tbca@gmail.com



Augsburg, Germany



tony500.github.io/Me

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN Mothertongue

GERMAN B2

ENGLISH C1

SPANISH C1

PROFILE

Full stack web developer with a problem solving forma mentis and a high social empathy. Experienced in working under pressure, aim to always provide the best solutions with the most effective tech stacks in order to achieve a quality that reflects the company values.

SKILLS

FRONTEND

HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Sass, React, Angular

BACKEND & STORAGE

Node.js, Express, Mongo, MySQL, Google Firestore

Agile Development, OOP, Strong Communication, Team Player

OTHER RELATED SKILLS

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Information Technology Branch I.T.I.S. H. Hertz, Rome (1998 - 2004) Graduated with 96/100

BACHELOR

Tor Vergata, Rome (2004 - 2009) Computer Engineering (2004 - 2009) Not graduated

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEV

Full Stack Wed Dev Course on CareerFoundry.com

2022 - Present

- Intro to web development (HTML/CSS), jQuery and pre/post processing
- Agile development knowledge and remote working core concepts
- GIT, Performance Analysis, Testing, Progressive Web Apps
- Designed/Developed/Analyzed/Optimized Frontend and Backend apps based on various tech (Node.js, Express, React, Angular)

HOSPITALITY

London/Sydney/Barcelona/Berlin 2011 - 2021

- Various roles in Hospitality in several venues around the world
- Managing teams to pursue company goals

JAVA EE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Zeropiù S.p.A.

2008 - 2011

- Java EE Application development
- Android development
- REST services

DATACENTER SPECIALIST

Telecom Italia | Consultant

2007 - 2008

- Datacenter Inspections
- Ticket managing (Remedy Software)
- System intervention on demand